sercle.com 2017-06-25

# SerCle Inc. Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy discloses our privacy practices and the possible uses of the information that we gather our software application (the “Application”) and via other submissions by you to SerCle, Inc. (together, the "Application and Services"). By using the Application and Services you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, including having your personally identifiable information ("Personal Information" as defined below) used in any of the ways described in this Privacy Policy, you may not be able to use certain parts or features of our Application and Services and may necessitate the revocation of the license to use the Application and Services. 

SerCle, Inc. (the “Company”) may update this Privacy Policy from time-to-time in our sole discretion. It is your responsibility to review the Privacy Policy for any changes each time that you use the Application and Services and you are bound by such changes. Use of the Application and Services by you following us posting a new privacy policy on our Application constitutes your acceptance of the Privacy Policy as modified. 

Information Collected   
The Company collects information on our users in various ways, such as, by your voluntary submissions, participation in services provided via the Application and Services, from third parties with your consent, and through cookie and other tracking technology. The Company collects the following information: 

Personal Information   
1 "Personal Information" refers to information that tells us specifically who you are, such as your name, phone number, email, postal address, and possibly information relating to certain support or customer service issues. In many cases, we need this information to provide to you many of the services that you may have requested. 

Submission of Reviews, Ratings, and Comments   
2 We collect information that you voluntarily provide as part of our Application and Services, including messages, posts, comments, responses, reviews, and ratings you submit through the Application and Services, ("User Generated Content"). The Company may in our sole discretion share your User Generated Content with others such as your business reviews. If you do not want certain information shared with others, you should not submit User Generated Content, or should not submit User Generated Content that contains information or Personal Information you do not want shared in this manner. Once you have submitted User Generated Content, we reserve the right to publish it in any medium to others. 

Aggregate Information   
3 We may collect general, non-personal, statistical information about the use of the Application. This information represents a generic overview of our users, including their collective viewing habits, and allows us and other third parties to modify information, promotions, offers and/or discounts on products and services based on user traffic and behavior. We collect this information in order to help enhance the Application and Services to make for a better experience. 

Third Party Information   
4 We may supplement information you provide to us with information from other sources, such as information to validate or update your address, payment card or other demographic and lifestyle information. We use this information to help us maintain the accuracy of the information we collect, to enable us to fulfill our products and services, to target our communications so that we can inform you of products, services and offers that may be of interest, and for internal business analysis or other business purposes consistent with our mission. 

Tracking Technologies   
5 We may use tracking technologies to assess our Application and Services, which may record information, including but not limited to, Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; software and operating system types; and dates and times that our Application and Services are accessed. 

Use of Information   
The information the Company collects is used in a variety of ways, including   
1 for internal review;   
2 to improve the Application and Services;   
3 to optimize third-party offers of products and/or services;   
4 to verify the legitimacy of reviews and ratings;   
5 to notify you about updates to the Application and Services;   
6 to let you know about products, services, and promotions that you may be interested in;   
7 to get reviews and ratings;   
8 for our marketing purposes and the marketing of discounts offered through our Application and Services by service contractors (collectively "Service Contractors");   
9 to fulfill and provide products and services, including personalized or enhanced services, requested by you; and   
10 internal business analysis or other business purposes consistent with our mission; and to carry out other purposes that are disclosed to you and to which you consent. 

Disclosures and Transfers of Information   
We do not disclose Personal Information to third parties, except when one or more of the following conditions is true: 

1 We have your permission to make the disclosure;   
2 The disclosure is necessary for the purpose for which the personal information was obtained;   
3 The disclosure is to financial service providers in order to fulfill and carry out the purchase and provision of goods and services requested by you;   
4 The disclosure is permitted by relevant law;   
5 The Personal Information to be disclosed is otherwise publicly available in accordance with the applicable law;   
6 The disclosure is reasonably related to the sale or other disposition of all or part of our business or assets;   
7 The disclosure is for our own marketing purposes, or, with your authorization, for the marketing purposes of third parties;   
8 The party to whom the disclosure is made controls, is controlled by, or is under common control with the Company;   
9 The disclosure is in our sole discretion necessary for the establishment or maintenance of legal claims or legal compliance, to satisfy any law, regulation, subpoena or government request, or in connection with litigation;   
10 The disclosure is in our sole discretion about users who we believe are engaged in illegal activities or are otherwise in violation of our Terms and Conditions, even without a subpoena, warrant or court order; or   
11 The disclosure is to outside businesses to perform certain services for us, such as maintaining our Application and Services, mailing lists, processing orders and delivering products and services, sending postal mail, providing marketing assistance, and data analysis ("Administrative Service Providers"), including Administrative Service Providers outside the country or jurisdiction in which you reside. 

Prior to sharing of your Personal Information with others, agreements are made between the Company and such outside parties to whom we are transferring data to provide for the allowable use and security of the transferred information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and applicable law. If the Company becomes aware that any such outside party is improperly using or disclosing Personal Information, it will notify that outside party and request that it take reasonable steps to cease such use or disclosure. 

We may provide certain Personal Information as a service to others for their marketing purposes. We may also disclose your name and address to Service Contractors when you submit User Generated Content relating to those Service Contractors. If you properly notify us that you no longer want us to share your Personal Information, we will cease sharing your Personal Information. However, except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not directly control the third parties to which we share such Personal Information and you will need to further notify such third parties directly if you would like them to cease use of your Personal Information. 

We may also disclose aggregate visitor data in order to describe the use of the Application and Services to our existing or potential business partners or other third parties, or in response to a government request. We may also share aggregated demographic and preference data with third parties to enable the provision of targeted information, promotions, offers and/or discounts on products and services. 

Data Security, Integrity, and Access   
The Personal Information you provide and we collect is stored within databases that we control directly or through our Administrative Service Providers. As we deem appropriate and as required by the applicable law, we use security measures appropriate for the sensitivity of the Personal Information and consistent with industry standards, including physical, organizational and technological protections, such as firewalls, to protect your Personal Information. We also use industry standard encryption technology to protect credit card and password information. However, since no security system is impenetrable, we cannot guarantee the security of our databases, nor can we guarantee that information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. 

Personal Information may only be accessed by persons within our organization, our third party service providers who require such access to provide you with the services indicated above, or any other party that you have provided us with authorization to share such information with.   
We retain Personal Information that we collect only as long as reasonably necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected or to otherwise meet any legal requirements. 

Your information may be transferred to, and maintained on, computers located outside of your state, province/territory, or country where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those where you live. If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, please be aware that we transfer Personal Information to the United States and process and store it there. As a result, this information may be subject to access requests from governments, courts, law enforcement officials and national security authorities in the United States according to its laws. Subject to the applicable laws, we will use reasonable efforts to ensure that appropriate protections are in place to maintain protections on the Personal Information. By submitting your Personal Information, you consent to having your personal data transferred to, processed, and stored in the United States. 

The Company may assign you a user ID and a password when you as part of your participation and access to the Application and Services. Your user ID and password may only be used by you and the members of your household. You may not share your user ID and password with anyone else, and you are solely responsible for maintaining and protecting the confidentiality of your user ID and password. You are fully responsible for all activities that occur under your user ID and password. You can access and update your login information on your "Manage My Accounts" webpage. 

Children's Privacy   
The Company does not intend the Application and Services to be used by individuals under the age of majority within the jurisdiction within which they reside without the supervision of a parent or guardian of majority age. The Company relies upon such parents or guardians to determine if the Application and Services is appropriate for the viewing, access, or participation by such individuals under the age of majority. If an individual under the age of majority uses the Application and Services, such individual may only use the Application and Services under the supervision of a parent or guardian of majority age. 

We do not seek or knowingly collect any Personal Information about children under 13 years of age. If we become aware that we have unknowingly collected Personal Information from a child under the age of 13, we will make commercially reasonable efforts to delete such information from our database. 

If you are the parent or guardian of a minor child who has provided us with Personal Information, you may contact us using the information below to request it be deleted. 

Governing Law; Visitors Residing Outside the United States   
This Privacy Policy and the privacy practices of the Company will be subject exclusively to the laws of the State of California. 

How To Contact us   
All requests, questions, concerns, or complaints about your Personal Information or this Privacy Policy, please contact our Privacy Officer by mail or email at the following: 

Attn: Privacy Officer   
SerCle, Inc.   
39180 Liberty Street, Suite 220D   
Fremont, CA 94538 

We welcome your questions and comments.
